>> Kyle Simpson: 要更好地了解原始值，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To get a better
understanding of how primitive values,
基本类型值，以及某些特殊值工作，
primitive type values, and
some of the special values work,
我们要跳进这一运动
we're gonna jump into this exercise.
在这次演习中，我们将会做一个聚聚。
In this exercise,
we're going to make a polyfill.
你要给我的
You're gonna define a polyfill for
我们刚刚聊过的是 Object.is 的实用程序
that Object.is utility
that we just talked about.
所以换句话说没有作弊
So in other words, no cheating,
你不能去看看现在的执行情况
you can't go look at the existing
implementation of it.
你要写你自己的对象就是这样
You're gonna write your own Object.is,
and in so doing,
在处理这些原始值的问题上得到一些实践
get some practice with the idea of
dealing with these primitive values and
他们的类型和转角情况之类的
their types and the corner cases and
things like that.
所以这里的指示是要定义一个对象。
So the instructions here talk
about defining an Object.is,
得有两个参数
it's gotta take two parameters.
请记住，将两个值作为两个单独的参数。
Remember it takes two values
as two separate parameters.
如果他们完全是同一件事，那就应该回到真实的状态。
And then it's supposed to return true
only if they're exactly the same thing.
平常你就用三大的，但是两个大角
Now normally you would just use a triple
equals for that, but the two major corner
三重等于的个案是 NaN 值和负零值。
cases on triple equals where it lies are
the NaN value and the negative zero value.
所以你要考虑的是
So you're gonna essentially
need to account for
那是第一次了如果你不在这些条件下
those first, and then if you're
not in one of those conditions,
那么三等同体会告诉你它们的价值是否相同
then the triple equals would tell
you if they are the same value.
所以这里的指示是关于处理 NaN 和负零点的问题。
So the instructions here talk about
handling the NaN and the negative zero.
您可以使用内置实用程序，如 number.isNaN ，但
And you can use a built-in
utility like number.isNaN, but
还有一种检查 NN 的方法
there's also a way of checking for
NaNs that isn't that.
看看你能不能把它弄明白
See if you can figure that out.
您还可以计算负数。
You can also figure out negative zeros.
最后一个小纸条是我们在定义一个聚聚
So one last little note here is
that we're defining a polyfill,
还有多填充图案如你所见
and the polyfill pattern,
as you can see here,
就是如果它还没有定义的话，你只会定义一些东西。
is that you only define something
if it's not already defined.
所以这才是真正的聚聚会是什么样的呢 ?
So that's what a real polyfill would look
like, is it would have that if statement
围绕您的定制功能定义。
wrapped around your definition
of your custom function.
这里的挑战是你几乎肯定在 JavaScript 中工作
The challenge here is that you're almost
certainly working in a JavaScript
已存在 Object.is的环境，为 ES6的 cuz ，因此 years back。
environment that already has Object.is,
cuz that was ES6, so years back.
所以如果你把它包在一个 if 语句中，你写的任何代码都不会
So if you wrap it in an if statement,
none of the code you write is ever gonna
你只会在客观环境中测试你自己
run and you're just gonna be testing
yourself against the built in Object.is.
因此，作为一个临时的黑客，我将禁用该声明。
So as a temporary hack,
I would disable that if statement.
你可以用字面意思说
You can disable it by literally
saying something like or
所以你总是在定义一个
true so that you're always defining one.
显然你不会在正常的聚聚中留下这个
You wouldn't leave that in,
obviously, in your normal polyfill.
但为了这次演习的目的，既然你在做什么
But for the purposes of this exercise,
since you're polyfilling something
已存在，请确保以某种方式禁用该语句，或者
that already exists, make sure that you
disable that if statement in some way, or
你就可以发表声明了好吗
you can just comment out the if statement,
okay.
但是记住这一点
But just keep that in mind.
你要在 ex.js工作
You're gonna be working in ex.js.
您会注意到在此文件中，我有许多控制台日志语句，并且
You'll notice that in this file I have
a bunch of console log statements, and
每个人都在为这个测试做点什么
each one of them is asserting
something about this test.
因此，目标是所有这些控制台日志语句都必须
And so the objective is that all of
these console log statements all have to
打印 true。
print true.
即每个调用都返回 true ，并且
That is that each one of these
calls all return true, and
每个调用都返回 false。
each one of these calls all return false.
你知道你有一个经过考验的时候
So you know you have a passing
test when you get all trues and
没有虚无的谎言
no falses printed out.
运行此代码的方法，您可以打开此文件并
The way to run this code,
you can open up this file and
从命令行直接在节点中运行。
run it directly in node
from the command line.
您可以将代码复制到控制台，并且
You could copy your
code into a console and
在控制台中运行它，例如在 Chrome 开发者工具中。
run it inside of a console,
like in your Chrome developer tools.
但是，您喜欢运行 JavaScript，
However you like to run your JavaScript,
不需要其他周围的信息
doesn't need any other
surrounding information.
但你要在上面定义你的对象
But you're gonna define your Object.is
polyfill here at the top, and
然后确定它是否通过了所有测试
then make sure that it pass all the tests.
这可能需要五到八分钟的时间，所以我们就休息了，
This would probably take someone between
five and eight minutes, so we'll break,
让你有机会做运动然后我们就回来
let you have some chances to work on
the exercise, and then we'll come back and
谈谈这个解决方案。
talk about the solution.
如果您有股票，需要提示，那么会为您提供解决方案，并且
If you get stock and you need a hint,
the solution is provided for you and
位于同一目录中的 ex.fixed.js 。
it's ex.fixed.js in that same directory.
好吧玩这个游戏玩得开心
All right, have fun with this exercise.